[{
        "Question": "Select question to ask",
        "Answer": ""
    },{
        "Question": "What do you see?",
        "Answer": "A large block is below the medium block. A blue loc_c location is below the large block. A medium block is on the large block. A large block is on the blue loc_c location. I see a green loc_a location and a green loc_b location"  
}, {
        "Question": "What is below the medium block 2?",
        "Answer": "A large block."
    }, {
        "Question": "What is below the large block 1?",
        "Answer": "A blue loc_c location."
    }, { 
        "Question": "What is on the green loc_a location?",
        "Answer": "Nothing."
    },{
        "Question": "What is on the green loc_b location?",
        "Answer": "Nothing."
    },{
        "Question": "What is on the blue loc_c location?",
        "Answer": "A large block."
    },{
	"Question": "Describe the medium block 2.",
        "Answer": "The shape is block. The size is medium. The volume is 2.0 . A large block is below the medium block."
    },{
	"Question": "Describe the large block 1.",
        "Answer": "The shape is block. The size is large. The volume is 3.0 . A blue loc_c location is below the large block. A medium block is on the large block. "
    },{
	"Question": "Describe the green loc_a location.",
        "Answer": "The shape is location. The color is green. The volume is 4.0 ."
    },{
	"Question": "Describe the green loc_b location.",
        "Answer": "The shape is location. The color is green. The volume is 4.0 ."
    },{
	"Question": "Describe the blue loc_c location.",
        "Answer": "The color is blue. The shape is location. The volume is 4.0 . A large block is on the blue loc_c location. "
}]
